let's look at the solution for the part
30 for one cycle quiz which is about if
this is the state at the beginning of
the cycle then during this cycle which
if any instruction will dispatch into
the Lu here and this instruction we
already saw in part two is going to free
its reservation station and it's already
executing so it will definitely not
dispatch again this instruction here
will capture its last remaining operon
during this cycle so it becomes eligible
for dispatch after that we said that in
the same cycle capture and then this
patch is allowed so this instruction
here is a candidate for dispatching we
are also going to issue this instruction
here into a reservation station but
because the issue and then this patch is
not allowed in the same cycle that means
that this instruction even if its
operands were ready would not be
eligible for dispatch now so the only
instruction eligible for dispatch is
this one which means that that's the one
that gets to dispatch if more than one
instruction were eligible for dispatch
then we would have to pick which one
dispatch is because we only have one
execution unit and in order to do that
we would actually need to be told what
are the rules for picking among
instructions fortunately we didn't need
that because only one is eligible for
dispatch